

Francesco Zaniol

Senior Frontend Engineer • Contractor / Freelance • Remote EU <u>fzaniol@gmail.com</u>

About

Hi, I'm Frank. I am a Senior Frontend Engineer with 10+ years of industry experience. I work remotely from Italy on a B2B contract basis, short or long term.

Quick links

- <u>Personal page</u>, a presentation of my professional background.
- <u>Linkedin profile</u>, a more detailed overview of my skills and experiences.

Top skills

VueJS • Nuxt • Typescript • ES5+ • Vanilla • Accessibility • PWA/SPA • Design System • Testing • HTML5 • CSS3 • SASS/LESS • Tailwind • Animations • Agile • Responsive Design • Git • API • Webpack • Vite • UX • GraphQL • Debugging • Performance • SEO • Cross-browser • Web Components • PHP • Laravel • Wordpress • DRY • Teamplayer

Work experience

MAIZE | H-FARM Innovation

Senior Frontend Engineer 2018-2023 (5 years 6 months) • Italy (Full remote) VueJS, TypeScript, Testing, Design System, Laravel

IE Agency

Lead Frontend Developer • <u>movember.com</u> 2014-2017 (3 years) • Melbourne, Australia Team Lead & Mentor, Agile, Design System, Testing, PHP, Zend

AKQA

Frontend Developer 2012-2013 (1 year 6 months) • Italy PSD to HTML, SASS/LESS, JavaScript, Animations

accessibletemplate.com

Founder
2012-2017 (5 years 2 months) • Worldwide
Joomla templates, Accessibility, Personal business

AWDD MEDIA

Frontend Developer
2010 (7 months) • Vancouver, Canada
Drupal, PSD to HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, HTML5

Education

Ca' Foscari University, Venice

Degree, Information Technology 2004 - 2008 (3 years 6 months)

Grade: 107/110

ITIS Max Plank

High school diploma, Information Technology 1999 - 2004 (5 years)

Grade: 100/100